<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>animation-review on Blog de Preminstrel</title>
    <link>https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/tags/animation-review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in animation-review on Blog de Preminstrel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>preminstrel@gmail.com (Hanshi Sun)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>preminstrel@gmail.com (Hanshi Sun)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:47:07 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/tags/animation-review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>86-Eighty Six Review</title>
      <link>https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/post/2022/04/15/eighty-six-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:47:07 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>preminstrel@gmail.com (Hanshi Sun)</author>
      <guid>https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/post/2022/04/15/eighty-six-review/</guid>
      
      <description></description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conan M24 The Scarlet Bullet  Review</title>
      <link>https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/post/2021/07/20/conan-m24-rreview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 23:53:14 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>preminstrel@gmail.com (Hanshi Sun)</author>
      <guid>https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/post/2021/07/20/conan-m24-rreview/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Actually, M24 is similar to other recent releases, which reasoning element is highly reduced while some unscientific and unbelievable phenomenon may happen. To be frank, I clearly know that it is a convert to cater more audience’s demand, including someone who is not interested in mystery stories. Although maybe it is an irreversible transformation, I still hope that M25’s performance can be better in this aspect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s discuss M24 itself. The background of M24 is the 2020 Tokyo Olympic Games, which was not successfully hold in the real world. I want to select some impressive plot  to discuss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Firstly, the meaning of &lt;em&gt;Scarlet Bullet&lt;/em&gt; matters. In the movie, Akai Shuichi plays a noticeable role that the bullet he shot unbelievably wounded the criminal and successfully rescued Conan and his sister who still does not know who he is. It’s an interesting design that Akai Shuichi’s nickname is “&lt;em&gt;Silver Bullet&lt;/em&gt;” and the bullet he shot this time is made of silver aimed to not be attracted by the magnetic force.  The Conan movies always uses color to ornament the title. This time the color is &lt;em&gt;Scarlet&lt;/em&gt;, which I think corresponds to the last name of Akai Shuichi and his family. “Akai” means a special kind of red in Japan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What’s more, the importance of the Haibara Ai is undoubted. Lots of  scientific phenomenon is explained by her, such as &lt;em&gt;quench&lt;/em&gt;. By contrast, Lan did not show the influence to the incident this time, which raised the unsatisfactory of many audience who belong to XinLan party. Although, actually, interactions between Conan and Ai remarkably increase in M24, I maintain the idea that it is not bad thing. Different from Lan, the life of Ai seems to be full of tragedies and frustrations while Lan almost owns everything she wants, including the love of Conan. Thus the shift of the perspective to character who maybe ignored really should be taken into consideration seriously. Okay, I admit that I prefer Ai to Lan. :-) What is a incredible thing is that someone insult others just due to the little amount of interactions between Lan and Conan is out of their expected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reasoning part is almost destroyed by extremely numerous occupation of contents. Sad to say, I can only accept it and contribute my ticket to the evil screenwriter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I sincerely hope that M25 may have more reasoning parts and attracting plots for our Conan fans who born before 2005.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uma Musume Review</title>
      <link>https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/post/2021/07/15/uma-musume/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 23:53:14 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>preminstrel@gmail.com (Hanshi Sun)</author>
      <guid>https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/post/2021/07/15/uma-musume/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eclipse First, the Rest Nowhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Uma Musume Pretty Derby has two seasons, I prefer the later season, adaption based on true story of &lt;em&gt;Tokai Teio&lt;/em&gt; (トウカイテイオー). The plot is ordinary, even you can preview the next race’s result. However, Cygames, the producer of Uma Musume anime, made it remarkably extraordinary through its expressive pictures. Comparing to season 1, from my point of view, season 2 takes a leap and noticeably wins more applause. The main character of it is Tokai Teio, different from main character of season 1, &lt;em&gt;Special Week&lt;/em&gt; (スペシャルウィーク), Tokai Teio’s life is not really going smoothly. Four fractures created the Tokai Teio’s miracle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;「母ちゃん化」makes Uma Musume a hit, ウマ娘 successfully presents characteristics of horse in the history and brings them to the same stage. To be frank, I am not interested in sports. However, Uma Musume makes me know that horse racing can be such enthusiastic. From the anime, unconsciously, I am exposed to knowledge related to horse racing, such as Triple Crown, 「天皇賞」,「有馬記念」. Every horse has its dream, the reason to race. The anime gives the horses personalities and dreams, which can be a significant factor to make it a success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-angle-of-horses&#34;&gt;The angle of horses&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;career&#34;&gt;Career&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of flash point of Uma Musume is that it makes horses have the dreams and emotions like people. Thus, horses have the reason to race for themselves, not for trainers or audience. The most iconic role is Tokai Teio, my favorite character. Tokai Teio lost her chance to achieve Triple Crown and Undefeated one. Due to it, she was confused that why she run and the real meaning of running. She wanted to give up running and turn to support others. However, another misfortune happened. After the victory of the Takarazuka Memorial, &lt;em&gt;Mejiro McQueen&lt;/em&gt; (メジロ マックイーン ) was unfortunately suffering from zonular ligament inflammation(悬韧带炎) on his left leg while preparing for the Autumn Emperor Award. Therefore, Tokai Teio decided to run again to encourage McQueen and she succeeded creating the miracle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://sm.ms/image/JxzwbpkN2fhs4WK&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://s2.loli.net/2022/04/14/JxzwbpkN2fhs4WK.jpg&#34; width=&#34;500px&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;failure--fractures&#34;&gt;Failure &amp;amp; fractures&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Comparing to Specil Week, Tokai Teio has the remarkable body ability and talent. Thus, at the beginning of the anime, Tokai Teio has won Double Crown in an invincible posture. However, due to her soft knees, she can boost easily than others while she can be vulnerable on another hand. Fracture ended Tokai Teio’s first dream. After fail to achieve her dream, Teio set up another dream: Undefeated and fail when competing with McQueen. Such failure and diseases depressed her, making her afraid of running and competing, just lowering her head and saying “I cannot”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://sm.ms/image/u1VjbmXZPlKRWx2&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://s2.loli.net/2022/04/14/u1VjbmXZPlKRWx2.jpg&#34; width=&#34;500px&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;friends&#34;&gt;Friends&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tokai Teio lost her mind and confidence. The trainer made her do some behind-the-scenes work. When doing such works, Teio’s state of mood has changed slowly. When asking McQueen why she runs, McQueen smiled and told her that because of she was looking forward Teio’s revival. Teio’s confuse vanished quickly and devoted to train herself as before. Finally, she achieved a miracle as promised successfully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://sm.ms/image/bY54qX9Hz8oMuJt&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://s2.loli.net/2022/04/14/bY54qX9Hz8oMuJt.jpg&#34; width=&#34;500px&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;history-based&#34;&gt;History based&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An interesting point is that every horse and race is based on the history authentically, including the results of races. Thus, Teio’s miracle is real history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;miracle&#34;&gt;Miracle&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is an undoubtedly miracle! Episode 13 express Teio’s unbreakable will and stubborn confidence remarkably. I cannot express it very preciously, I regard that only when you watch such scene, will you feel the flow of emotions. Teio’s words and Narrator’s words can make me cry even just imagine the picture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://sm.ms/image/ZIg4mnFYAUMPxBz&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://s2.loli.net/2022/04/14/ZIg4mnFYAUMPxBz.jpg&#34; width=&#34;500px&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;「トウカイテイオーがきた！え？トウカイテイオーがきた？」&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;「僕は何度も苦付けてきた、あの時も、あの時も、誰より苦付けてきた！」&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;「誰よりも悔し気持ちなたのは僕だ！」&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;「誰よりも勝ちたい気持ちが強いのは僕だ！」&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;「絶対に譲らない！」&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;「絶対に、絶対に、絶対は僕だ！」&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;「勝負だ！」&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;「トウカイテイオーだ！トウカイテイオーがきた！」&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;「トウカイテイオーも来ている！さあ、残り２００を切りました！残り２００を切った！」&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;「ビワハヤヒデ！トウカイテイオー来たっ！トウカイテイオーが来たっ！トウカイテイオーが来た！」&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;「ビワハヤヒデとトウカイテイオー！ ダービー馬の意地を見せるか！」&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;「トウカイテイオーだ！トウカイテイオーだ！トウカイテイオ～！奇跡の復活～！！」&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let miracles become synonymous with will in that the authenticity of history proves it all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align=center&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://sm.ms/image/UD1kOXPvNlGKxEn&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://s2.loli.net/2022/04/14/UD1kOXPvNlGKxEn.jpg&#34; width=&#34;500px&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
