<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conan on Blog de Preminstrel</title>
    <link>https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/tags/conan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Conan on Blog de Preminstrel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>preminstrel@gmail.com (Hanshi Sun)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>preminstrel@gmail.com (Hanshi Sun)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 23:53:14 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/tags/conan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Conan M24 The Scarlet Bullet  Review</title>
      <link>https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/post/2021/07/20/conan-m24-rreview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 23:53:14 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>preminstrel@gmail.com (Hanshi Sun)</author>
      <guid>https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/post/2021/07/20/conan-m24-rreview/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Actually, M24 is similar to other recent releases, which reasoning element is highly reduced while some unscientific and unbelievable phenomenon may happen. To be frank, I clearly know that it is a convert to cater more audience’s demand, including someone who is not interested in mystery stories. Although maybe it is an irreversible transformation, I still hope that M25’s performance can be better in this aspect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s discuss M24 itself. The background of M24 is the 2020 Tokyo Olympic Games, which was not successfully hold in the real world. I want to select some impressive plot  to discuss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Firstly, the meaning of &lt;em&gt;Scarlet Bullet&lt;/em&gt; matters. In the movie, Akai Shuichi plays a noticeable role that the bullet he shot unbelievably wounded the criminal and successfully rescued Conan and his sister who still does not know who he is. It’s an interesting design that Akai Shuichi’s nickname is “&lt;em&gt;Silver Bullet&lt;/em&gt;” and the bullet he shot this time is made of silver aimed to not be attracted by the magnetic force.  The Conan movies always uses color to ornament the title. This time the color is &lt;em&gt;Scarlet&lt;/em&gt;, which I think corresponds to the last name of Akai Shuichi and his family. “Akai” means a special kind of red in Japan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What’s more, the importance of the Haibara Ai is undoubted. Lots of  scientific phenomenon is explained by her, such as &lt;em&gt;quench&lt;/em&gt;. By contrast, Lan did not show the influence to the incident this time, which raised the unsatisfactory of many audience who belong to XinLan party. Although, actually, interactions between Conan and Ai remarkably increase in M24, I maintain the idea that it is not bad thing. Different from Lan, the life of Ai seems to be full of tragedies and frustrations while Lan almost owns everything she wants, including the love of Conan. Thus the shift of the perspective to character who maybe ignored really should be taken into consideration seriously. Okay, I admit that I prefer Ai to Lan. :-) What is a incredible thing is that someone insult others just due to the little amount of interactions between Lan and Conan is out of their expected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reasoning part is almost destroyed by extremely numerous occupation of contents. Sad to say, I can only accept it and contribute my ticket to the evil screenwriter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I sincerely hope that M25 may have more reasoning parts and attracting plots for our Conan fans who born before 2005.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
