<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Game on Blog de Preminstrel</title>
    <link>https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/tags/game/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Game on Blog de Preminstrel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>preminstrel@gmail.com (Hanshi Sun)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>preminstrel@gmail.com (Hanshi Sun)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 22:18:01 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/tags/game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tales of Arise</title>
      <link>https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/post/2022/05/05/tales-of-arise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 22:18:01 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>preminstrel@gmail.com (Hanshi Sun)</author>
      <guid>https://preminstrel.github.io/blog/post/2022/05/05/tales-of-arise/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tales of Arise is the first video game of Tales Series I played. I am impressed by its remarkable landscape and typical characters. However, I think it should be a gap between it and Xenoblade Chronicles 2. The plot of TOA (Tales of Arise) is a little conservative that I can even predict the end. Moreover, the music exactly does not match the plot or scenes. Somehow, I regard it as pale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;characters-and-plots&#34;&gt;Characters and Plots&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The male protagonist is the typical JRPG role. And the emotional or love details of the male and female protagonists are adequately described, which is commendable. The heroine is born to be untouchable and the hero can touch her thanks to his sealed nervous system. Therefore, typically, it is a &amp;ldquo;boy meets girl&amp;rdquo; story. Immense quantity of little dialogues falshcards effectively contribute to the constructing the characters and its personalities. Maybe because of the shortage of budget or time limit, the last phase of the plot seems a little hash and does not provide enough time for me to enjoy and digest. Thanks to the kindness of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bandainamcostudios.com/en/&#34;&gt;BANDAI NAMCO Studios Inc.&lt;/a&gt;, the end is a satisfactory for me and most players. But, you know, cause the XB2 (Xenoblade Chronicles 2) made a great impact to me, such plots or characters are not that attractive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;scenes&#34;&gt;Scenes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scenes of TOA is really a big deal, which has made a milestone for JRPG area, proving that the scene of JRPG can be that impressvie. It could be the new game egnie or rendering method that makes such wonderful world and characters with exactly pragmatic consumption of GPU and CPU memory. It is a really advancement for Tales Series and JRPG! Congratulations!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;music&#34;&gt;Music&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be frank, expect for the two OP and ED, the music is terrible, especially the background music. I hope the BANDAI could be careful dealing with DLC sale strategy because I heard that the music can be improved by the DCL purchase. The OP and animation perfomance is really remarkable, but I have no more words for overall music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;combat-system&#34;&gt;Combat System&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I truly appreciate the clever artificial intelligence operation, which even is better than me. Thanks to the beatiful and impressive combat aniamtion, the system can be better than I think. The strategy can be set in advance, which is friendly. However, the quantity of boring side quests and repetitive monster battles is not that satisfying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plots: ★★★&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Characters:  ★★★&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scenes: ★★★★★&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Music: ★★&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;System: ★★★&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
